http://www.optcorp.com/pages/privacy-policy

a
adm ag optical airylab antares antlia filters apm apogee asa astrel instruments astro products astro systems astro-physics astronomik astrotrac astrovid astrozap atik ats avalon
b
baader barska bka bob's knobs bookstore borg
c
caelum celestron chroma chroma open coronado custom scientific
d
daystar dba denkmeier optical dc-3 dreams dew-not diffraction ltd.
e
eva-dry explora-dome explore scientific
f
field tested systems fli
g
gerd neumann
h
hobym hotech hubble optics hutech hyperion astronomy
o
officina stellare omegon oouk opt opt telescopes optec opticron optics future optolong orange county telescope orion
p
pacific design parallax pegasus astro pentax peterson pier-tech planewave primalucelab
q
qhy qsi
r
radian revolution imager rigel
s
santa barabara scientific saving hubble sbig shannon telescopics sharp star shelyak sirius tech sky-watcher software bisque solarscope stargps starguy starizona stark labs starlight instruments starlight xpress stellarmate stellarvue
t
takahashi tec technical innovations tele vue telegizmos teleskop service telrad thermo knight thousand oaks tpo
u
unihedron unistellar used equipment
v
vaonis vixen
w
warren keller william optics
x
xagyl
New to the hobby? Check our 2020 telescope buying guide
Still not sure what is the right gear for you?Read our 101 article or get in touch. We will be glad to help.
By type
Refracting
Dobsonian
Reflecting
Ritchey-Chretien
Cassegrain
Apochromatic
Optical Tube Assemblies
Want to capture Special Events Comets, eclipses
Still not sure what is the right gear for you?Read our 101 article or get in touch. We will be glad to help.
Visual
Lunar / Planetary
Deep Sky
Solar
Deep Space Imaging
Lunar / Planetary
Deep Sky
Solar
Privacy Policy
Contact Us Shipping Return Policy OPT Financing Price Match Guarantee Product Warranties Pricing Disclaimer Privacy Policy
customer help Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for optcorp.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
Find out what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 800-483-6287 or via email.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.
Cookies
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
Sharing of Information
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Last Updated: Oct 20, 2020
{formbuilder:24707}
{formbuilder:24706}
{formbuilder:24817}
{formbuilder:24818}
{formbuilder:26097}
